[Music]
let's take a relaxing break and leave
cyber stress behind come with me to a
clearing a stream a mountaintop and
finally to outer space at each stop in
our journey I will share with you
methods that may help you relieve the
physical and mental stress that comes
from long hours at your computer feel
your serpent within suspended now
between the sky and the earth and
imagine your favorite mountain could be
a hill any high place where you like to
be around round and round now reverse it
coming in in in tickling is a wonderful
way to relieve tension
[Music]
[Applause]
I thank you for moving with me from
place to place I hope you will continue
to visit these places and incorporate
them into your work day and remember
relax take breaks relax take breaks
[Music]